decide.com 2013-04-25

# Privacy Policy / Decide

Last updated: October 24, 2012.

Decide, Inc. ("Decide") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting the Web site located at www.decide.com and the other websites and mobile sites of Decide which link to this Privacy Policy (the "Sites"), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Decide Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your Decide experience. Here are the types of information we gather.

#### Information You Give Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on the Sites or provide us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as providing our services to you, responding to your requests, and communicating with you. Examples of this information include location data to provide for local pricing, information that allows us to monitor prices over time for products you may be watching, information regarding your product searches, information regarding your clicking on a link to a retailer's website, information you provide to establish and manage your membership, information you communicate to us by phone, email or otherwise, information when you contribute content to our blog or participate in other community features, and information that you provide when you offer us feedback. Such information may include your name, address and phone numbers, credit card information, and other financial information.

[ When creating a Decide account, or connecting your already existing Decide account with your Facebook account, we will also receive and store the following information from Facebook, Inc. ("Facebook") your name, user name, password, profile picture, unique Facebook identifier and access token, gender, birthday and email address.

If you connect your Decide account to Facebook, we will make available and/or share your Facebook user name and your Facebook profile picture to other Decide users.

If you have connected your Decide account to Facebook, we may share with Facebook certain information related to your use of the Sites, and such information may be published on Facebook's websites or services. You can choose to disable automatic publishing on Facebook of your activities on the Sites in [the preferences pane]. Information shared to Facebook will be attributed to the Facebook account to which your Decide account is connected. Facebook's use of such information and any information it collects from your use of or on its service is governed by Facebook's privacy policy and Decide's use of information is governed by this Decide Privacy Policy. You understand and agree that you need to consult both privacy policies to amend or delete personal information which has been provided to Facebook. If you do not wish for such use of data to take place, you should not agree to share information about your activities on the Sites to Facebook and/or adjust your settings to deactivate such sharing. Information no longer shared on Facebook may continue to be available to Decide and its users, and may be used as described in this Privacy Policy. ]

#### Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Sites or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Decide on other Web sites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

#### Mobile:

When you download or use apps created by Decide, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services. 

#### E-mail Communications:

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Decide if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your [Customer Communication Preferences](https://www.decide.com/account/settings/).

#### Information from Other Sources:

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. For example, we may receive confirmation of your product purchases from retailers to which the Sites provide links.

### What About Cookies?

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide features on our Sites, and personalized advertisements on other Web sites. 

The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Decide's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to use any Decide products and services that require you to Sign in. 

### Does Decide Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below. 

#### Aggregated Data:

We analyze, publish and share aggregated level data for marketing purposes, including, for example, information identifying popular items, or most searched for items. 

#### Third-Party Service Providers:

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include, sending postal mail and e-mail, , analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

#### Promotional Offers:

Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Decide customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your [Customer Communication Preferences](https://www.decide.com/account/settings/).

#### Business Transfers:

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell portions of our business, or buy other businesses. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice (unless the customer consents otherwise). Also, if Decide or substantially all of its assets are acquired, then customer information will be one of the transferred assets. 

#### Protection of Decide and Others:

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Decide, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

#### With Your Consent:

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

We (or our service providers that handle credit card processing for us) reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order (but, as may be expected, transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing). 

### Which Information Can I Access?

Decide gives you access to a range of information about your account and your interactions with Decide for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. <https://www.decide.com/account/>

### What Choices Do I Have?

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of Decide premium features 

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your [Customer Communication Preferences](https://www.decide.com/account/settings).

### Are Children Allowed to Use Decide?

The Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use the Sites and under no circumstances should you provide personal information to us. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete that child´s information from the Sites.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Decide, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at Decide, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
